http://www.ibew56fcu.org/privacy

HomeLoansLoan RequirementsSignature Share SecuredLoan SpecialsVehiclesStudentHome EquityMini MortgageFinancing StatementLoan ApplicationCo-Maker StatementSavings
Share AccountsIRA AccountsEducational SavingsYouth Savings Savings RatesShare CertificatesChecking AccountsFunds AvailabilityDirect PaymentServicesMembershipAboutLinks
Kelly Blue BookUsed Car GuideAmerican Education ServicesFree Annual Credit ReportSavings BondsMYCUCard Visa Purchase AlertsNCUA Financial EducationWaldameer ParkKennywood ParktruSTAGE InsuranceEnterprise Car RentalContact
menu
IBEW Local 56 Federal Credit Union was chartered in 1961 - Once A Member ... Always A Member
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
FACTS
WHAT DOES THE IBEW LOCAL #56  FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information may include:
- Social Security number and account balances
- Payment history and credit history
- Transaction history
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share information as described in this
noitice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons IBEW Local #56 Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does IBEW Local #56 FCU share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes-
Yes
No
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes-
Yes
We don't share
Questions?
Call (814)455-2270 or (800)723-7800
What we do
How does IBEW Local #56 FCU protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does IBEW Local #56 FCU collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
- open an account or apply for a loan
- make a wire transfer or give us your contact information
- show us your driver's license
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
- sharng for affiliates everyday business purposes- information about your creditworthiness
- affiliates from using your information  to market to you
- sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
IBEW Local #56 FCU has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
- Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, government
agencies, check printers, card services, credit reporting agencies, data
processors, and corporate credit unions
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
- Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group's MEMBERCONNECT
Top
HomeLoansLoan RequirementsSignature Share SecuredLoan SpecialsVehiclesStudentHome EquityMini MortgageFinancing StatementLoan ApplicationCo-Maker StatementSavings
Share AccountsIRA AccountsEducational SavingsYouth Savings Savings RatesShare CertificatesChecking AccountsFunds AvailabilityDirect PaymentServicesMembershipAboutLinks
Kelly Blue BookUsed Car GuideAmerican Education ServicesFree Annual Credit ReportSavings BondsMYCUCard Visa Purchase AlertsNCUA Financial EducationWaldameer ParkKennywood ParktruSTAGE InsuranceEnterprise Car RentalContact
Search ...
My CU CardStar Non-Surcharge ATMFee SchedulePrivacy PolicyNewsletterPrivate Student Loans
